

CONTACT ME AT

Noida, Uttar Pradesh

drishtibahl68@gmail.com

(+91) 8800401109

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/drishti-bahl-37a487196/

https://github.com/drishtibahl12

DIGITAL PORTFOLIO - https://drishtibahl12.github.io/MyPortfolio/

SKILLS

- Public Relations
- Communication
- Team Player
- Kali Linux
- Wireshark
- Nmap
- HTML5 &CSS3
- Computer Networking
- Nessus tool

CERTIFICATIONS

- CEH v11 by EC-Council Ongoing
- Security+ by CompTIA Ongoing
- Cyberops Associate by
 Cisco Networking Academy
- HackNU 3.0 by NIIT University

PROJECTS

- Password crackingIn this project I cracked the passwordusing basics of Python Language
- Impact of Video Knowledge base (R&D Project)lin this project, an open K.B was made using HTML5 &CSS3
- CRUD Application
- Evolution from 5G to 6G

DRISHTI BAHL

CYBERSECURITY UNDERGRADUATE

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a passionate Computer Science student at NIIT University. My research and career interests lie at the nexus of **Cybersecurity** and **Networking**. **Enthusiastic** and dedicated to my work in the field of management and networking. **Determined** to be **an asset**.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cybersecurity Analyst Intern

Craw Security | March 2022 - July 2022

- Learnt about the identification of cyber security solutions with respect to different attacks.
- Learnt about the implementation of the solution in real time world.
- Gained a good knowledge about basics of Networking and Security.

Interned at Cisco

Cisco Networking Academy | April 2021 - Sept 2021

- Polished my Cybersecurity Skills like Nmap Scanning, Wireshark,
 System Hacking, Vulnerability Analysis
- Learned the fundamentals of Networking and performed specific tasks in a practical scenario.
- Learned about the Packet Tracer software and built basic network structure.

Head of Public Relations at Sinusoid

NIIT University Tech-Fest | 1st Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

- Plan, Develop and execute the publicity and brand establishment strategies.
- Introduced the Fest Ambassador program in order to build strong networking for the fest.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

NIIT University - Specialisation: Cybersecurity

Bachelors of Technology - Computer Science & Engineering | C.G.P.A.: 7.31 | Aug 2019 - May 2023

Ahlcon Public School (XII) - Science(Non-Medical)

C.B.S.E. | **Secured: 94.8**% | April 2018 - March 2019

The Khaitan School (X) - Secondary

C.B.S.E. | **Secured: 9.8/10.0** | April 2016 - March 2017

POSITION OF RESPONSIBILITY

- Buddy Mentor in NanoEPL, NIIT University
- SPOC at TedXNIITUniversity
- Public Relations Head at Sinusoid